At last, today's main event is about to begin!
Here's 250-pound Super Kong of the Dragon's Lair
with 5 wins and one loss.
Listen to him roar! What a monster!
The challenger from the Tiger's Lair
debuts in this match today!
He is Gold Tiger Mask,
also known as the Yellow Devil.
Will he emerge victorious from his debut match?
Or will he become the latest victim
of Super Kong's win streak?
A one fall match with no time limit!
A hair-raising battle is set to begin!
A barrage of kicks and punches!
Both sides look sharp!
However, Gold Tiger Mask
seems to have a slight edge.
Or not!
Super Kong unleashes a roar of wrath!
"10 years ago"
"Children's Home"
Everybody, gather round!
Make two lines starting here.
Older kids, take care of the younger ones.
Does everyone have their booklets?
Yes...
All right, then. Let's go!
Naoto?
Ruriko, what's the matter?
Naoto. Hurry up, or you'll be left behind.
Look! Elephants! They're huge!
Over there too! See?
They are big, aren't they?
Take a good look, okay?
Naoto!
Naoto.
Where have you been?
Mommy! Daddy!
Thank goodness!
Don't take off like that.
Let's go.
Okay.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
You're lying. It's all over your face.
You too, Ruriko.
Meaning what?
I don't want to get kicked out of
this Children's Home.
So, you know that the property manager came?
I am so sorry!
Mr. Wakatsuki, I didn't come here for apologies.
Read this.
If you can't pay, you must move out.
It's in the lease.
I'm doing my best to cut costs
as much as possible.
As I explained before...
this is an orphanage
that relies solely on donations.
A field trip tomorrow?
You should pay rent first, don't you think?
It's the only trip we go on every year.
Our children look forward to this.
Well, we are taking legal actions now.
Please! If you could ask the landlord
to give us one more month...
We've already done this three times!
We can't do this anymore!
Please! I'm begging you!
For the love of God, Mr. Kinoshita!
The children have nowhere else to go.
This is their only home.
I'm begging you!
I can't do anything.
Please!
If I were strong enough, I'd beat him up.
I wish my mom was still alive.
I guess we won't be able to stay together.
Hey.
This is for you.
Take it.
That way, you will always remember me.
I'll remember you!
Just keep it.
Naoto?
What's the matter?
Date Naoto.
Come with me. And you'll be strong.
You have special power.
Naoto?
Naoto, where are you going?
Who are you, mister?
If you could have one wish granted...
Name one.
To be strong.
I don't want to be alone again.
I see. Then come with me.
To where?
To the Tiger's Lair.
Naoto...
Dad! Akira!
What happened?
Naoto is gone!
Naoto...
Naoto's missing!
Naoto!
Naoto...
Are you listening?
Sorry. What is it?
Were you recruited by Mr. %, too?
Yeah, I was. You too, Dan?
I think everyone here has been.
In your case, he just had pity on you.
What's his problem?
You don't want to talk to him.
How come?
He burned his family's house down.
Shut your mouth!
He wouldn't have a place to go back to, then.
Get off, you brats!
Come on! Move it!
This whip is for lazy bums!
Hurry up, already!
Move.
Follow me.
Hurry up and walk!
We're here,
This is your new home. The Tiger's Lair.
Line up!
Single file!
Welcome to the Tiger's Lair.
There's no reason to fear.
You should consider yourselves lucky.
You've been selected as part of this family.
I will be your father and...
your mentor too.
You have older brothers. They arrived before you.
Follow the teachings of the Tiger's Lair,
and this is what you'll become.
They are the greatest fighters on Earth.
They have trained for years...
to become absolutely unbeatable.
A glorious future awaits only those
who endure harsh training.
These are no ordinary masks.
It took me years to perfect these Tiger Masks.
These masks are capable of unlocking
the wearer's deepest potential beyond his limit.
The white one unleashes power.
The gold one enhances speed.
And the one that is superior
to both in every aspect is...
this black Tiger Mask.
Complete the arduous training here.
If you are deemed worthy,
you will have the honor of
wearing one of the masks.
Listen carefully.
Train hard and...
embody the soul of the beast in your body.
Strive for a strength...
That no man can defeat!
Here are the commandments of the Tiger's Lair.
Repeat after me.
Yes, madam...
First, mercy is for the weak.
First, mercy is for the weak...
Second, fairness is the excuse of fools.
Second, fairness is the excuse of fools...
And finally, what is the reason why we fight?
For the glory of the Tiger's Lair!
For the glory of the Tiger's Lair...
Once again!
First, mercy is for the weak...
Second, fairness is the excuse of fools...
What do we fight for?
For the glory of the Tiger's Lair...
You could get yourselves killed!
A weak man can't survive.
That's the fate for those who live here.
Good job today, everyone.
I prepared this special dinner
with the greatest care.
Here are the perfect meal
and dietary supplements for your needs.
Don't be picky. Eat it all.
Stop it.
Just give me your meat.
All right.
Here you go.
Don't mess with me!
Who do you think I am?
I'll wear the black Tiger someday.
You little turd!
Come on.
Why, you!
Boys, stop it!
Calm down!
Come get me!
You two! Stop!
Let go of me!
I said, stop!
Stop!
A deadly attack, the Tiger's Lair Plug.
Stop, do you not understand?
I must ask Mr. X to punish you.
Remember, you'll pay for this.
Line up.
Still have energy to fight each other?
I'll make a point of working you harder tomorrow.
Fighting among brothers is not allowed here.
You are the smallest
and you still thought you could stop the fight?
If Maki hadn't stepped in,
you would have been crushed.
I had to help my friend, sir.
Mercy is for the weak.
The strong one always wins
and the winner is always right.
Don't ever forget that.
Winning is the priority
over anything and everything.
But remember...
there are two types of strength.
The strength here and...
The strength here.
Strengthen here.
And you'll be stronger than any other man.
Jo!
Don't look down!
Keep your eyes up and pull yourself upward!
Why didn't you save him?
One less competitor to worry about.
Mercy is for the weak. Repeat it.
Mercy is for the weak...
Repeat it.
Mercy is for the weak.
Oh, it's you, Dan.
I was getting worried about you.
I wonder if I should've saved him.
It's not your fault.
If you tried to help, you would've fallen too.
Are we supposed to keep going on like this?
We must follow the commandments,
First, mercy is for the weak!
Second, fairness is the excuse of fools!
And what do we fight for?
For the glory of the Tiger's Lair!
Listen.
We train not only your body,
but also your mind here.
Study the cycle of the flames,
and get to the other side.
No one at your level
has ever passed this challenge.
Does anyone dare to give it a try?
Enough. Back in line.
Next?
Naoto!
Way to go!
Dan, Jo, and Naoto.
10 years have passed since you arrived here.
You three have survived and proven yourselves
worthy of the title of Tiger Mask.
Receiving the honor of the Mask
does not mean the end of the training.
He seems relaxed and confident.
At this very moment,
anew chapter of your destiny has begun.
The main event is about to start!
The Black Tiger Mask versus the Salamander!
This is the debut match for the Black Tiger.
His potential is unknown.
His first opponent is pretty tough!
Here comes the Salamander,
unbeaten champion, from the Dragon Cave.
He is known for his unparalleled ruthlessness.
He'd do anything to win!
He seems relaxed and confident.
He's so confident that
he's already doing his victory dance.
He boasts ten out of ten victories.
He is the greatest!
The flame is bigger and stronger than ever!
And there goes the bell!
Salamander hurls his chain!
Black Tiger is wrapped up!
He's on the chopping block!
The Tiger Back Breaker!
He killed in a split second!
If you blinked, you missed it!
Our exceptionally talented rookie
brought down the house!
I made good money. I appreciate your work.
My pleasure.
I can see that the Tokyo Office is in good hands.
Of course.
A talent like the Black Tiger
comes around only once in a decade.
You've found someone
worthy of wearing the masks you invented.
I'm still improving them.
The question is whether the guys
can keep up as the masks evolve.
In your current shape,
you can fight at full force only for a limited time.
If it stays on too long,
your body will begin
to deteriorate from the inside.
Know the limit of your mask
and fight accordingly.
You always make the same moves.
You lucked out this time.
When is your debut match?
Next week.
Good luck.
Thanks.
How much did you make? Show it to me.
Look at this wad of cash!
So, what's next?
We're gonna party all the way with this money!
Here you are.
Enjoy your meal.
Hey, look at that.
Hi.
Let's go.
Cold shoulder, right?
Naoto, come on.
Naoto.
Would you like a drink?
Me?
Dan!
Bourbon on the rocks.
Me too.
All right.
Here you go.
Cheers!
Are you okay?
Don't mock me!
Another one.
We've got juice, if you want.
We've got juice.
Shut up! Just give me another one.
Me too.
How old are you?
How about you, baby?
What are you doing here?
Show me how the Black Tiger fights.
What did you say?
Let go of me!
If you wanna fight him,
you've gotta fight me first.
Pardon me.
Take it outside, will you?
I'll get you first, as you wish.
Better be ready for me.
Could you please leave?
I can't wait for my match next week.
Next time I'll buy you drinks.
Naoto.
Hey, are you listening?
Stop!
Naoto! Hey!
Keep the change.
Naoto.
This is it.
What's going on?
What are you looking at?
I was raised here.
Here?
Why are you hiding?
Ruriko.
Mercy is for the weak.
Fairness is the excuse of fools.
For the glory of the Tiger's Lair.
Naoto.
You're thinking about that girl, aren't you?
Ruriko...
Ruriko, wasn't it?
It's been 10 years and you still remembered.
I knew it was her the minute I saw her face.
Was she your first love?
She wouldn't remember me, though.
Of course not. You and I have changed too.
So, Dan...
Here's 250-pound
Super Kong of the Dragon's Lair
with 5 wins and one loss,
He's ready to fight!
I've gotta go.
Don't lose.
Of course not!
I already have a plan for
how to spend the money after the match.
Don't steal my signature attack.
What is it?
The Tiger's Lair Plug.
This is the debut match
for the challenger from the Tiger's Lair.
I'm not into this kind of stuff.
Hey! This is the Tiger Mask!
Awesome!
Watch this!
What's this?
Is it live?
Gold Tiger grabs his legs!
Here it comes! Giant Swing!
He's spinning the giant Kong
with incredible speed!
Kong is totally disoriented!
It's a human centrifuge!
Now Kong is thrown to the ropes!
He bounces back! What's the next attack?
It's the Lariat!
It's explosive! He's going flying!
Super Kong is airborne!
It's a total knock-out!
Gold Tiger earns an amazing victory,
winning his debut match!
Gold Tiger is responding
to the roaring cheers in the house!
He has a bright future ahead of him
as a professional wrestler!
What is happening here?
White Tiger Mask bursts into the ring!
What in the world...
Is it a family feud?
That idiot!
This is unbelievable! The crowd is on fire!
Kill him...
Kill him?
The crowd is calling out, 'kill him!"
How will Gold Tiger handle White Tiger's challenge?
He's completely drained from the match!
What the...
You asked for this.
I'll take you on first.
Jerk...
Unbelievable!
They rang the second bell!
Too slow.
Is that all you've got?
Darn it!
My body...
Is that it?
What a dirty trick!
Fairness is the excuse of fools.
Dan!
What perfect timing!
Hey! Leave him alone!
Jo! Stop it!
Stop!
Dan!
Hang in there!
Dan! Get up!
Get up! Dan!
Get up!
Dan! Get up!
Dan...
You're just a big talker.
Dan!
I don't need any other Tiger Mask.
It's not fair! The match is over!
Let go!
Stop...
We don't think so!
I'll take you on later.
Darn it!
Stay out of this!
A German suplex to finish him off!
It's fatal!
Cold-blooded, bad-ass White Tiger rules!
Dan, hang in there!
Dan!
Naoto...
Sorry.
I can't buy you a drink tonight.
Don't worry.
I'll go get a doctor.
Your knee is completely shattered.
Any pain?
I'm all right.
I'm sorry.
No worries.
You're finished as a fighter.
It's the loser's fate.
If you cross me again,
you're going to die.
No...
This can't be!
Hey, Dan!
You were alive a moment ago!
Calm down.
You've gotta be kidding!
Wake up, Dan!
Open your eyes, Dan!
I'm not scheduled to see you today.
What happened to Dan in the dressing room?
Please tell me the truth.
The truth?
Have you seen a race horse with a broken leg?
It is totally useless.
Ending its life is the best option for both parties.
Dan wasn't an animal.
He was a human being.
He wasn't just human.
He was a fighter too.
A fighter who cannot fight is not worthy of living.
You can't really mean that.
Tell me, Black Tiger Mask,
why do you fight?
I...
An enormous amount of money
moves behind the scenes at those matches.
The Tiger's Lair is spread throughout the world.
We use the money from the matches
to rule the Underworld.
And you fight to earn money.
I'm sorry that you lost your friend.
It pains me too.
Take as much as you want.
Have fun for a change.
Thank you very much...
for waking me up.
What are you saying?
Why do you think
I clothed an orphan like you,
fed you and trained you
to become the greatest fighter?
If you choose to be ungrateful
and walk out the door for good,
I'll hunt you down no matter where you go.
And you'll pay for it with your own life.
Make a wise decision.
I don't belong here anymore.
How was it in Europe?
Berlin, Paris, Rotterdam.
Each branch has promising talent.
I see. Where are you going next?
I'll stop in Hawaii and the U.S. mainland.
I expect a thorough search.
The Tokyo Branch might be going downhill.
I understand, sir.
Ouch!
He woke up! The bum is up!
Trespassing is not allowed.
Please leave.
I'll call the police.
I'm sorry. Somehow I ended up here.
What's going on?
Ruriko.
And you are...
Naoto?
Hey, let's go outside.
Hey mister, what are you doing here?
Mister? Me?
He's not a stray cat.
He's a grown man.
He should take care of himself.
Just for a little while.
We used to live together, you know.
But he ran away and caused many problems!
Dad was so worried, he lost half his hair.
He was lost for 10 years, but now he's back?
Sounds fishy.
He might've escaped from prison.
He's not like that.
Kick the ball!
Oh, man!
Over here! Give me the ball!
It's not like we have enough hands around here.
Maybe he can work here,
but only if he wants to.
Taking care of kids
is more than just playing with them.
But, I guess...
He can work for room and board.
Thank you, brother.
Oh, no.
You're doing it wrong.
Let me show you. Like this.
We're home!
All right. Got it.
Keep it up.
Manabu had an accident! He peed!
I remember when you broke
dad's favorite fishing rod.
Really?
Yest
I don't remember.
Come on...
The house looks far better than
what it used to be back then.
It must've been very hard for my dad.
Now I know.
Your smile hasn't changed at all.
Really?
So, Naoto...
Where have you been
and what were you doing all this time?
I was...
working at a zoo.
The face you make
when you lie hasn't changed, either.
It's not a lie.
A rich gentleman took care of me.
And I worked at his zoo.
But we had a fight recently and [ left.
What is the zoo called?
Tiger's Lair.
Tiger's Lair?
What is that?
I've never heard of such a zoo!
It's in the middle of nowhere.
Let's get going.
Well, Christmas is coming up.
Is there anything you want?
Let's see...
A backpack. Manabu needs one for school.
You are the only Tiger Mask left.
Give me your blessing to fight him.
Hey, everyone! Dinner time! Come back in!
Wash your hands!
Slow down! No need to push!
Remember to gargle too!
"Merry Christmas”
Naoto!
Watch out for the hook.
Throw this over there, and the fish will bite.
So, Naoto...
What's your plan for the future?
For my future?
Only if you want...
Why don't you work full time for us?
Maybe get certified?
Think about it seriously, will you?
Thank you.
Naoto! We caught one!
Are you sure?
Yeah! I'm positive!
Let me see.
See? I'm reeling it in!
Excuse me. Pardon me.
Are you all right? Do we have everyone?
Mr. Akira went in to get Manabu!
Akira did?
There he is!
Are you okay?
Yeah, we're all safe.
Thank goodness, but what happened?
I don't know the cause, but...
One of the kids saw a stranger
when the fire broke out.
Stranger?
A tall man with a beard, I heard.
Let's go.
Everyone, we need to get away.
Naoto!
I've been waiting for you.
You had the Children's Home
set on fire, didn't you?
You sent him.
You broke the rule of the Tiger's Lair.
But if you beg for mercy, I may forgive you.
Mercy is for the weak.
Isn't that right?
I raised you like my son
and gave you power and wisdom.
But you got lost in your feelings?
And you couldn't become strong in the true sense.
What a shame!
Power and wisdom mean nothing...
if your heart is lost.
You can't call that strong!
You killed my best friend.
And you robbed the children of their home.
I won't let you go on like this!
He's turned against the Tiger's Lair.
Great Tiger, kill off this fool.
Great Tiger?
You are finished.
Everything you have is now mine to destroy.
Not only your life...
But the girl and all those little children.
No, you won't!
It's time for you to wake up!
Mr. X...
Give me more power.
Jo!
I expected more from him.
But it was too much for him.
The newest mask went to waste.
Jo...
I won't forgive you!
Never hurt anyone ever again!
Farewell, Tiger Mask.
Naoto!
I know you will come back to me.
Keep your guard up.
This place will be closed.
But the Tiger's Lair has
a network throughout the world.
What will you do?
I won't run away.
I'll keep on fighting.
Naoto.
We need to buy a new one.
It's my fault.
I'm so sorry.
Why is that?
How is it your fault?
I shouldn't have come back here.
My dad...
thought of you as his own son.
He believed you'd come back
until the day he died.
So, when you showed up,
I was very happy.
Thank you.
You accepted me unconditionally.
I appreciate that.
I was so happy just being here.
Are you leaving again?
For the first time, I have someone I want to protect.
That's why I'm leaving.
Promise me...
that you'll be back.
I will because...
this is my home.
Don't ever think I'm done with you.
Tiger Mask!
Miss Ruriko. This is for you.
Thank you.
"To Miss Ruriko Wakatsuki,
Chibikko Children's Home"
"Merry Christmas”
"10 million yen"
"In honor of the sudden passing of Mr. Hisao Maki"